Used to be a big deal.
曾经很厉害
Stupid doorknob,
蠢门把手
come off!
掉下来啊
Nailed it!
好了
Can't believe that
原来你的最佳计划
was your best plan.
就是这样啊
Come on, guys, let's go touch
来吧 伙计们 我们去
some expensive stuff.
碰碰贵的东西
Aah!
啊
Dewey!
杜威
Aah!
啊
I'll put the marbles back,
我会把弹珠放回去的
I swear!
我发誓
Who sent you?
谁派你们来的
Ma Beagle? Glomgold?
比格妈妈吗 格莱姆高吗
Answer me!
回答我
Uncle Scrooge!
史高治叔叔
Uncle Scrooge?
Oh, my gosh,
天哪
the nephews!
是侄子啊
Wait, you know us?
等等 你认识我们
Of course! Researching
当然 调查
Mr. McDuck and his family
麦克老鸭先生和他家人
is kind of my hobby.
算是我的爱好
What?
什么
What are your blood types?
你们什么血型
What's Donald really like?
唐纳德到底是什么样
Who's the evil triplet?
你们三个谁最坏
Louie.
路易
Eh.
呃
Tell me everything!
都告诉我吧
Um, we live
呃 我们和叔叔
with our uncle?
住在一起
On a boat?
住在船上吗
Go on.
接着说
Kinda it.
差不多说完了
We're just a normal,
我们只是普通
boring family.
又无聊的一家人
Normal, boring? Hah!
普通 无聊 哈哈